// creating an array and passing the number, questions, options, and answers
let questions = [
    {
    numb: 1,
    question: "Who is the father of C language?",
    answer: "Dennis Ritchie",
    options: [
      "Steve Jobs",
      "James Gosling",
      "Dennis Ritchie",
      "Rasmus Lerdorf"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 2,
    question: "Which of the following is not a valid C variable name?",
    answer: "int $main;",
    options: [
      "int number;",
      "float rate;",
      "int variable_count;",
      "int $main;"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 3,
    question: "All keywords in C are in______",
    answer: "LowerCase letters",
    options: [
      "LowerCase letters",
      "UpperCase letters",
      "CamelCase letters",
      "None of the mentioned"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 4,
    question: "Which of the following cannot be a variable name in C?",
    answer: "volatile",
    options: [
      "true",
      "friend",
      "volatile",
      "export"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 5,
    question: "Which keyword is used to prevent any changes in the variable within a C program?",
    answer: "const",
    options: [
      "immutable",
      "mutable",
      "volatile",
      "const"
    ]
  },
  

  {
    numb: 6,
    question: "Which of the following typecasting is accepted by C language?",
    answer: "Widening & Narrowing conversions",
    options: [
      "Widening conversions",
      "Widening & Narrowing conversions",
      "Narrowing conversions",
      "None of the mentioned"
    ]
  },

  {
    numb: 7,
    question: "Where in C the order of precedence of operators do not exist?",
    answer: "None of the mentioned",
    options: [
      "Within conditional statements, if, else",
      "Within while, do-while",
      "Within a macro definition",
      "None of the mentioned"
    ]
  },

  {
    numb: 8,
    question: "What is an example of iteration in C?",
    answer: "all of the mentioned",
    options: [
      "for",
      "while",
      "do-while",
      "all of the mentioned"
    ]
  },

  {
    numb: 9,
    question: "Functions can return enumeration constants in C?",
    answer: "true",
    options: [
      "false",
      "true",
      "depends on the compiler",
      "depends on the standard"
    ]
  },

  {
    numb: 10,
    question: "How many number of pointer (*) does C have against a pointer variable declaration?",
    answer: "No limits",
    options: [
      "7",
      "127",
      "255",
      "No limits"
    ]
  },
  
];